I got my first real sixth string
Boiled out the five and done
Played it till my fingers bled
Was a summer of 69
Me and some guys from school
Had a band and we tried real hard
Timmy quit, Jody got married
I should've known we never get far
Well, when I look back now
The summer seemed to last forever
And if I had the choice
Yeah, those won't all be there
Those were the birthdays of my life
Ain't no use in complaining
When you got a job to do
I spend my years down at the job in
And that's when I met you, yeah
Standing on your mama's porch
You told me that she waits for me
All the years, days of my life
Back in the summer of 69
When it was my new time
The times are changing
Look at everything that's coming down
Times went up when you got old sixth string
So you're back to wonder why it went wrong
Standing on your mama's porch
You told me that it was
Those were the best days of my life
Back in the summer of 69
Oh, yeah
What's that?
Nobody
I said who's that?
I said nobody