Ah, this is by everybody who's been restored.
DeLaurin's coming at ya.
Get up, come on y'all, let's sing this song.
Ah.
Oh.
Got a story to tell you
Of some things that have been through but I'm here
Yo, I'm here.
Oh, I'm here.
I like that.
Got some bugs, got some doubt
Oh, you only knew.
To the ground, but I'm here
Right now, I stand before you.
Oh, I'm here.
Ah.
That too, that's so important.
I love that.
More than what we'll remember.
But I'm here.
I stand here.
Oh, I'm here.
Thank you, Lord.
I had some sunshine and some rain.
Yeah.
Or they can't some pain.
I'm here.
Oh, I'm here.
Oh, listen.
My daughter first.
God touched me.
He lived.
Ah, he delivered.
He said, I'm so free.
Now my heart is mended.
My heart is mended.
Oh, I'm whole again.
You see, there's no change.
Yeah, guess what?
Got my liberty.
I'm here.
Ah.
Oh, say it, y'all.
Ah, ah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, he set my soul.
He set my free.
Anybody free like me.
My heart is mended.
Anybody mended.
I'm whole again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't say, he is.
Guess what?
He is.
Oh, where the spirit is, there's a limit.
I am here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I may have some scars.
I am here.
But I'm here.
Circumstances.
Still got some circumstances.
I'm still here.
But I'm still here.
It's a point man.
Oh, let's take it out.
Say that again, y'all.
With his stripes.
Oh, oh, oh, I'm here.
Anybody here like me.
With his stripes.
I'm here.
I like this part.
We have some scars.
Yeah.
I am here.
I'm here.
Circumstances.
I'm still here.
It's a point man.
Many disappear.
I am here.
We have some scars.
Circumstances.
I'm still here.
I'm here.