She's a empty canvas on the sheets of clay
The world lay spread out before me as her body would still
Oh, five horizons revolved around the song
I see her through the song
Now the air I tasted and breathed
There's taking a turn and all I know is she gave me all
That she wore out my bitter hands
Shaked beneath the clouds of what was everything
All the pictures said, all been washed in black
Tattooed everything
I take a walk outside
I'm surrounded by some kids I've been
I can feel their laughter
So why do I see her?
I'm twisted thoughts that span around my head
I'm spinning, oh, I'm spinning
How quick the song can drop away
Now my bitter hands
Create a broken glass of what was everything
All the pictures said, all been washed in black
Tattooed everything
All the love gone bad
Turned my world to black
Tattooed all I see
All that I am
All I'll be
I know someday you'll have a beautiful life
I know you'll be a star
Being somebody else's sky
But why?
Why?
Why can't it be?
Or can't it be?