I'm like the water when your ship rolled in that night
Rough on the surface but you cut through like a knife
And if it was an open shut case
I never would've known from that look on your face
Lost in your current like a priceless wine
The more that you say, the less I know
Wherever you stray, I follow
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
Life was a willow and it bent right to your wind
Head on the pillow I could feel you sneaking in
As if you were a mythical thing
Like you were a trophy or a champion ring
There was one prize I'd cheat to win
The more that you say, the less I know
Wherever you stray, I follow
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
You know that my train could take you home
Anywhere else is hollow
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
Life was a willow and it bent right to your wind
They count me out time and time again
I come back stronger than a 90's trend
Wait for the signal and I'll meet you after dark
Show me the places where the others gave you scars
Now this is an open shut case
I guess I should have known from that look on your face
Every bit and switch was a work of art
The more that you say, the less I know
Wherever you stray, I follow
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
You know that my train could take you home
Anywhere else is hollow
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
The more that you say, the less I know
I follow, begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
You know that my train could take you home
Anywhere else is hollow
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man
Hey, that's my man
That's my man
Every bit and switch was a work of art
Hey, that's my man
I'm begging for you to take my hand
Ripped my plans, that's my man