I follow the Moscow down to Gonkipok listening to the wind of change
An august summer night soldiers passing by listening to the wind of change
The world is closing in, did you ever think that we could be so close like brothers
The futures in the air can feel it everywhere, blowing with the wind of change
To the magic of the moment, an aglory night where the children of tomorrow be my wings in the wind of change
Walking down the street, distant memories are buried in the past forever
I follow the Moscow down to Gonkipok listening to the wind of change
To the magic of the moment, an aglory night where the children of tomorrow be my wings in the wind of change
The wind of change blows straight into the face of time like a storm wind that will ring the freedom bell for peace of mind
Lady of Alalaka sing what my guitar wants to sing
To the magic of the moment, an aglory night where the children of tomorrow be my wings in the wind of change