I'm singing into my fire
Oh, all flowers in time Bend towards the sun
I know you say that there's no one for you But here is one
Oh, flowers in time Bend towards the sun
But here is one
I know you say that there's no one for you But here is one
Bend towards the sun I know you say that there's no one for you
But here is one
Keep it going in me We can travel and
Fading farther from me With your face in my window glow
Wait for me, sweet widow It's okay to be in vain
To me, yeah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,