Please snap them cross-line
It looks like they're spinning the crime
And ooh, it's your favorite side
Tempted murder of my mind
Can't even have a conversation
Without you breaking
Character tagging, going chasing
Two faces don't be a cold thing
Wherever you came from
Before I let you get inside my brain
And get in line, get in line
And lie, lie, lie, lie
You were not the first to try
That I luck next time
Party, but you couldn't put me
You tried your act, you can't keep up
Did you miss me bitch?
Did you reminisce?
Running my death certificate
You almost got away with it
But the rapist snits
Now you got to admit to
Your crimes, lie so, so slight
Well, you're gonna be like
Like, like, like, like
Stopping so tight
Yeah
But you just had to decide to
Get in line, get in line
And lie, lie, lie, lie
You were not the first to try
That I luck next time
Party, but you couldn't put me
You tried your act, you can't keep up
Your party, but you couldn't put me
Back in the first step
We sucked the shit that did this
Exceed, talking up in toss and
Welcome to live in that to me
My life in the first step
We sucked the shit that did this
Exceed, talking up in toss and
Welcome to live in that to me
That's to me, that's to me
Party back
Thought you could put me in a
You tried your best, but you would never