Halboy Carter? Time to strike a match and ride up this Duke George.
I am the one, I am the one now, just tell me how to.
Boy she got that water, think man got that water.
Don't act like you don't know.
Giddy up, giddy up.
Don't pay me in gold.
Back outside, I'm on the road.
Giddy up, giddy up.
When the sun goes down.
It's night of night of pain.
You can hear her body howl.
It's night of pain.
You hear her eye in me like howl.
I'm on the side of a patch.
I'll drive your man when a hangman coming down.
She's a tyrant.
Every time I ride it, every time I ride it.
Make it look so good.
Try to justify it.
Boy you know they're looking for me.
How we gonna hide it?
Try to look hydraulic.
I am such a tyrant.
Every time I ride it, every time I ride it.
I don't like to sit up in the saddle.
Boy I got it.
Just relax, I got this.
I got that exotic.
It's so so hypnotic.
I am such a tyrant.
So you with me or not?
Throw it back.
Shoot up the bar.
To tell a lie we don't remember.
And after that, stop.
Giddy up to me.
At a scene of 5'9".
To confine what a tragedy.
Trying to get away.
Riding you while we trying to get your way.
That's so sexy and I know it.
And I'm afraid to show it.
Baby I'm go-de-baby I'm go-ing.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm the run-run.
Tie me on the shoulder when you reload the gun.
Tyrant.
Every time I ride it, every time I ride it.
Make it look so good.
Try to justify it.
Boy you know they're looking for me.
How we gonna hide it?
Try to look hydraulic.
You're a tyrant.
Did you get used to the haunting?
The haunting.
You're just sending me.
She got that water.
Hangman got that water.
Don't act like you don't know.
Giddy up, giddy up.
Don't pay me in gold.
Back outside, I'm on the road.
Giddy up, giddy up.
When the sun goes down.
Can't hear this body howl.
Giddy up, giddy up.
Don't dig a dent.
Can't leave me alone.
If I do, if I don't.
Okay.
Tyrant.
Every time I ride it, every time I ride it.
Make it look so good.
Try to justify it.
Boy you know they're looking for me.
How we gonna hide it?
Try to look hydraulic.
I am such a tyrant.
Every time I ride it, every time I ride it.
In the end, this will sit up in the snare.
Oh boy, I got it.
Just relax, I got this.
I got that exotic.
This hip's so hypnotic.
I am such a tyrant.
Answer me now.
You owe me a debt.
You stole him from me.
I hate it.
I hate you now.
Just tell me how.
Tell me how.
I hate it.