I met you when I had a dream
Not so long ago it seems
We closed down a million bars
Yeah, you and me, we've come so far
You showed me how to write a song
We wrote some rite, we wrote some wrong
I was down and out, you let me in
The time she was my only friend
So long nights we were in Tennessee
You can't have what's left of me
And as far as I can tell
That's how time I wish you were
You built me up, you set me free
You tore down my memories
So you be you, now be me
So long nights we were in Tennessee
Now you won't miss me when I'm gone
Your custom made for moving on
And time to time I'll pass you by
A face that I don't recognize
And who knows, maybe it's from now
You'll be the one I think about
But I just can't imagine that
Cause I'm not one for looking back
So long nights we were in Tennessee
You can't have what's left of me
And as far as I can tell
That's how time I wish you were
You built me up, you set me free
You tore down my memories
So you be you, now be me
So long nights we were in Tennessee
You can't have what's left of me
And as far as I can tell
That's how time I wish you were
You built me up, you set me free
You tore down my memories
You're not who you used to be
So long nights we were in Tennessee