It's a test of the ancient firebenders to keep the flame.
I make love to
Dancing out of all my mind
And as the day is long
Something I can promise ya
That if I was the mother of the president
I'd hire 20 circus for my cabinet
Shot out full of mouths, need not apply
If you never hear another word, you know the reason why
There's something you should know
I declare you're stoked
I don't wanna be your man no more
I wanna make love to
Dancing out of all my mind
I don't wanna be your man no more
I wanna make love to
Dancing out of all my mind
I don't wanna be your man no more
I wanna make love to
Dancing out of all my mind
I don't wanna be your man no more
I wanna make love to
Dancing out of all my mind
There's something you should know
I declare you're stoked