25 years and my life is still trying to get up that great big healer of hope for a destination.
I realized quickly when I knew I should that the world was made up of this brotherhood of man
for whatever that means.
In Sui Christ sometimes when I'm lying in bed just to get it all out what's in my head
and I, I didn't feel any, a little peculiar.
In Sui wake in the morning and I step outside and I take a deep breath and I get real high
and I scream for the top of my lungs what?
In I said hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I said hey.
In Sui Christ sometimes when I'm lying in bed just to get it all out what's in my head
and I scream for the top of my lungs what?
In Sui wake in the morning and I step outside and I take a deep breath and I get real high
In I said hey, hey, hey, hey, I said hey.
What's going on?
25 years and my life is still done to get up that great big healer of hope for a destination.