So if you're lonely
You know I'm here waiting for you
I'm just a crosshair
I'm just a shot away from you
And if you leave here
You leave me broken, shattered, and lie
I'm just a crosshair
I'm just a shot, then we can die
Even here, with you
Hey, don't you know you say you
I say, I say you don't show
Don't move, time is slow
I say, you say I say
Move this could die
I smooth this could die
I want you to take me out
I know I hope you're leaving here
Oh, I know I believe in him
I know I believe in him
With you
Hey, don't you know you say you
Don't know I say
In this could die
Take this could die
I want you to take me out
I move this could die
I smooth this could die
Come on
Believe in him
I know I hope you're leaving here
I know I believe in him
With you