Came up to the surface I cannot remember
How long I've been swimming, drowning
Gets out grown accustomed to all of the sharks
And we're not really breathing
Now I won't just mind the gap I'll fill it
If I'm gonna eat this mosquito I'll have to thank it
I haven't really made the most of this life
From your honest bed back Whatever don't taste right
One time I told my heart to shut up
But I know that I can't win back her to us
I don't at least add much to the both of us
To fell out the neck for this dull conversation
I'd shop in my whip But what's my motivation
Don't need to be clever to tell you that I'm just
A total mess and then I must throw that old self away
If I don't get right now I will always
Eat what's to gain, sleep with the snakes
Here in this cold grave
I haven't really made the most of this life
From your honest bed back Whatever don't taste right
One time I told my heart to shut up
But I know that I can't win back her to us
I don't at least add much to the both of us
I was waiting for this to happen to me
But nothing's happening
I feel my skin as the sun burns it
And something in me sets light on it
Cause one more look might change it all
One more word might change it all
One more try might change it all
One more look might change it all