I told you about living in the US of hate, don't you know that I'm a gangster of love?
Let me tell you people that I found a new way, and I'm tired of all this talk about love.
In the same old story, we were going to settle words about the good and the bad and the poor.
And the times keep on changing so I'm keeping on top of every fat gap who walks through my door.
I'm a space cowboy, that you are ready for that.
I'm a space cowboy, I'm sure you know where it's at, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was born on this rock and I've been traveling through space since the moment I first realized
what all you fast-talking cats would do if you could. You know I'm ready for the final surprise.
There ain't no way around it, ain't nothing to say that's gonna satisfy my soul deep inside.
All the prayers and sobares keep the whole place uptight, love it keeps on getting darker outside.
I'm a space cowboy, that you are ready for that.
I'm a space cowboy, I'm sure you know where it's at, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've seen your showdown, slowdowns, lost and found, turn around, support and on military shirts.
I keep my eyes on the prize on the long-thoughtened skies and I don't let my friends get hurt.
All you black-roofed schemers, power-tripped dreamers, better find something new to say.
Cause you're the same old story, it's the same old crime, you've got some heavy dudes to pay.
I'm a space cowboy, that you are ready for that.
I'm a space cowboy, I'm sure you know where it's at, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.