Wipe away those tears child, there's no need to cry
Stand up on your feet now, lift your head up high
Now wait till tomorrow to lay down your sorrow
Freedom is here today
Wipe away those tears child, and put down your shame
Oh, I see L.M.T. Gray
The heavens waking, angels in jubilation
Bad storms beckoning, the darkness breaking
I bet the devil shaking, somebody celebrate
I see L.M.T. Gray
Wipe away those tears child, there's no need to cry
Stand up on your feet now, lift your head up high
Now wait till tomorrow to lay down your sorrow
Freedom is here today
Wipe away those tears child, and put down your shame
Oh, I see L.M.T. Gray
I hear the heavens waking, angels in jubilation
Bad storms beckoning, the darkness breaking
I bet the devil shaking, somebody celebrate
I see L.M.T. Gray
Wipe away those tears child, go and tell the news
What started in the garden was finished in the tomb
It's all reversed, the apple occurs three days in the ground
Christ our Lord is risen, death couldn't hold him down